Mother of Flies is a horror film directed by John Adams.
When a young woman faces a deadly diagnosis, she seeks
dark magic from a witch in the woods...
but every cure has costs.
Mickey, played by Zelda Adams.
Solveig, played by Toby Poser.
Jake, played by John Adams.
Ruthie at Reception, played by Lulu Adams.
Oncologist, played by Trey Lindsay.
Harry, played by Noble Wilson-Eiden.
The 29th Fantasia International Film Festival  opened on July 16 in Montreal, Quebec,
Canada, with American neo-Western black comedy film Eddington, by Ari Aster.
The Canadian Trailblazer Award was presented to Hungarian-born Canadian filmmaker George Mihalka, the director of the
1981 slasher film My Bloody Valentine, and Sheila McCarthy, Canadian actress and singer during festival.
Pascal Plante, a Canadian film director and screenwriter served
as jury president for Compétition Cheval Noir.
The seven of the competition’s eight categories awards were announced on July 26, with the jury awarding Mother of Flies, a horror–fantasy film by John Adams,
Zelda Adams, and Toby Posner, with the Cheval Noir Award for Best Film, marking the first time a United States production has received this award.
The festival closed on August 3, 2025 with dog sex adult comedy Fixed, by Russian-American animator, producer–director, Genndy Tartakovsky,
who was also honored with 'Cheval Noir Career Achievement Award' along with Danny Elfman, American film composer, and musician.
In the Audience Awards announced on August 5, 2025, Best International Feature Gold was
awarded to 2025 French film Flush, a thriller comedy by Grégory Morin.
The tone is dark.